♪
THERE'S REALLY SOMETHING
ABOUT THE FIRST GIRL
YOU PLAY DOCTOR WITH.
MAYBE IT'S COSMIC OR SOMETHING,
OR PERHAPS IT'S JUST THAT
SHE'S SEEN YOUR PACKAGE
AND DIDN'T RUN AWAY SCREAMING.
WHATEVER IT WAS, ALLISON AND I
WERE MADE FOR EACH OTHER,
A PERFECT FIT.
SO WHEN HER FAMILY MOVED AWAY,
I-- I KNEW THAT SOMEDAY,
SOMEHOW, FATE WOULD BRING US
BACK TOGETHER.
♪ HAPPINESS ♪
[ Allison ]
BERKE.
♪ STOP
I BEEN THINKIN' OF YOU ♪
♪ LOOK IN MY HEART
AND LET LOVE ♪
♪ KEEP US TOGETHER ♪
♪ YOU ♪
♪ YOU-DOO-DOO-DOO ♪
♪ YOU BELONG TO ME NOW ♪
OH, THANKS, HONEY.
YOU KNOW,
THE GUESTS GET SO CRANKY
WHEN YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
THEIR MUSIC.
NOW, YOU CAME HOME
SO EARLY LAST NIGHT.
DON'T MAKE IT TOO FLAT.
IS EVERYTHING OK WITH ALLISON?
NO, NOT REALLY. SO MAYBE WE CAN
TALK ABOUT IT--
UH, BERKE, YOU KNOW THE RULE.
WHEN WE'RE NOT
FEELING SUNNY, WE--
I DON'T REALLY WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT HERE.
I BELIEVE THE WORD IS SHARE.
FRANK, HON, APPARENTLY
BERKE HAS A PROBLEM
WITH ALLISON.
WHAT'S THE STORY, DUDE?
A LITTLE SNAFU IN THE OLD
CHANNELS OF COMMUNICATION?